以下事件发生于  下午4点至5点之间
The following takes place between 4:00 P.M. and 5:00 P.M.
事件实时发生
Events occur in real time.
目标出现
It's him.
见鬼
Damn it.
没机会开枪
I couldn't get off a shot.
原地待命
Stand by.
等他出来再干掉他
We'll get him on the way out.
曼纽尔
Manuel!
曼尼
Hey, Manny!
Manny!
曼尼
Hey, Manny!
喂
Yes?
让毛利西奥接电话
Put Mauricio on the phone.
-维克多  -让毛利西奥接电话
- Victor? - Just put Mauricio on!
他死了
He's dead.
什么
What?
头上挨了一枪
Someone shot him in the head.
到底出了什么事
What the hell is happening?
目标出现
I see him.
正在离开大楼
He's leaving the building.
准备就绪
I'm set.
停
Stop.
不是他
It's not him.
他跑不了多远
He can't be far.
目标朝你去了  灰色轿车
Coming at you! Gray sedan!
目标脱离射程
Target is out of range.
撤
Move out.
911报警中心  请讲
911. What's your emergency?
我要报告一起车辆盗窃
Yes. I want to report a stolen vehicle.
车牌号SNE-15C5
License plate SNE-15C5.
杰克
Jack?
小乖乖  我们商量过了  记得吗
Sweetheart, we already talked about this, remember?
你得叫我外公
You're supposed to call me "Grandpa."
但你看起来不像个外公呀
You don't look like a grandpa.
其实我也这么觉得
Couldn't agree with you more.
这卡通真没意思
The cartoon I turned on is boring.
好吧  那我们换个台
Okay. We'll find another one.
这是当代最大胆的外交提议
This is the boldest diplomatic initiative we've seen in a generation.
也许能为整个区域
It could finally lay a foundation for real peace
奠定全面和平的基础
throughout the entire region.
鲍勃  总统可谓是在这次谈判上
Well, you know, Bob, the president's certainly betting her legacy
赌上了她的政治生涯
on the success of these negotiations...
外公  这不是卡通片
Grandpa! This isn't a cartoon!
好吧
Okay, okay.
一群白熊
A sloth of bears...
就看这个  我喜欢这部
This one! I like this one!
一群奶牛
A mob of cows
一群绵羊
A herd of sheep...
喂
Yeah?
老爸  抱歉我们晚了
Hi, dad. Sorry we're late.
路过联合国大厦必须绕行
They're redirecting everyone around the UN.
没关系  我们相处很好
It's all right. We're doing fine.
动物园之行如何
How was the zoo?
实话说
Well, to be honest with you,
我们基本是在不断地奔波于
we spent most of our time just going back and forth
黑熊与北极熊之间
between the black bears and the polar bears.
我忘记跟你说  她正在熊熊热
I forgot to mention that she's going through a bear phase.
她明白自己所爱那是最好
Well, she certainly knows what she wants.
她让我想起你
She reminds me of you.
真有趣
Well, that's funny.
我常对斯蒂芬说  她让我想起你
I always tell Stephen how much she reminds me of you.
我们过几分钟就到
Anyway, we'll be there in a few minutes.
收到  别担心
Okay. Don't worry.
到时在大厅见
We'll meet you in the lobby.
好的
Great.
听起来他们处得不错
Sounds like they had fun.
当然啦
They always do.
怎么了
What's wrong?
刚来时  我跟他提过搬去洛杉矶的事
We talked to him about moving to LA the night we got here.
嗯  他说要考虑一下
Yeah. He said he'd think about it.
之后  他对此事只字不提
Yeah, and he hasn't mentioned one word about it since.
今晚我们都要走了
And we leave tonight.
或许他还得定期就医
Well, maybe he has to check with his doctors.
不是  医院两周前就让他出院了
No, they cleared him two weeks ago.
他的治疗已经结束了
He's finished with treatment.
搞不清楚
I don't know.
我父亲独自生活时间太久
My father has been on his own for so long.
也许他已经忘记了如何与人相处
Maybe he doesn't know how to live any other way.
你怎么不再问他一次
Why don't you just ask him again?
我父亲可不喜欢被人问两次
My father is not the type of person you ask twice.
我可以替你问他
If you want, I can do it.
联合国前方为您报道
Here at the United Nations,
白宫发言人刚刚确认
a white house spokesman just confirmed
泰勒总统与哈桑总统
that presidents Taylor and Hassan
稍后将立即召开联合新闻发布会
will be holding a joint press conference later this hour.
众人广为期待哈桑总统
It is widely expected that president Hassan
将宣布撤除其国的核武器项目
will announce the dismantling of his country's nuclear weapons program.
哈桑总统发表声明说  此次谈判
President Hassan has stated that he considers these negotiations
是历史性的成功  是其国家的新纪元
a historic success and a new beginning for his country
也是整个中东地区的新纪元
and the entire mideast region.
我相信我们已经达成了共识
I believe that that is a reasonable compromise.
总统先生  我们还有一些问题需要澄清
Now, Mr. President, let's move on to the issue of verification.
您最新提案的文字有些语意含糊
The language in your latest proposal is vague.
我来说清楚
Let me be clear.
我的国家同意放弃核武器的开发研制
My country agrees to abandon the pursuit of nuclear weapons
并愿意接受国际原子能组织的监督
with full International Atomic Energy Agency safeguards.
总统先生  我们的条件
But our terms, Mr. President,
是要由美国派出监督团队
were that the inspectors themselves would be American,
而非国际原子能组织
not IAEA.
恕我直言  总统阁下
With respect, Madam President,
贵方一再要求这点  但我们从未让步
your side pushed the point, but we never conceded.
也恕我直言
With respect,
贵方在这点上从未显示过诚意
your side has refused to negotiate the point in good faith.
若没有美方人员在场
Without Americans on the ground--
我们当然不会让一个几百人的团体
Surely, we're not going to let the nationality of a few hundred men--
我们不想引发争论
Verification has no teeth.
只有美国是可信的  是吗
So, only the United States can be trusted,
国务卿先生
Mr. Secretary?
这就是你向全世界传达的信息
This is the message that you sent to the rest of the world
你还问我们为什么不想协商
and then you wonder why we don't want to negotiate.
法哈德
Farhad.
总统阁下
Madam President,
请原谅我弟弟的莽撞
please excuse my brother's passion.
他只是为我们的国家考虑
He only wants what is best for our country.
可以理解
I understand.
但此问题解决之前  无法继续讨论其他事项
But we need to resolve this issue before we can move forward.
新闻发布会即将召开
And ideally, before the press conference,
我们只剩下不到一小时了
which gives us less than an hour.
总统阁下
Madame President...
如果我的革命卫士
what would your congress say
驻扎在您的国土上
if my revolutionary guard
国会会有什么反应呢
was stationed on your soil?
我国国会也持同样的态度
It's the same with my national assembly.
即便我同意了  我国议会也不会批准
Even if I agreed to this, they would not ratify it.
毕竟  我不是皇帝
After all, I'm not a king.
我也不是女皇
Nor I a queen.
真是太不幸了
Too bad for both of us.
我提议暂时休会
I'd like to adjourn
我们与各自团队商议一下
and discuss this issue with our respective teams.
没问题
Of course.
你知道  他在从政之前是做推销的
You are aware he was a salesman before entering politics.
卖家用电器
Household appliances.
他肯定卖掉了不少电冰箱
You want to bet he sold a lot of refrigerators?
想个办法  满足他的要求
Find a way to give him what he wants.
总统阁下
Madam President...
我意已决
You heard me.
想办法让监管计划得以施行
Try to make the inspections work.
他是个难得的领袖
This man is a once in a lifetime leader.
他已经停止了对恐怖组织的支持
And he has already suspended his support for terrorist organizations,
私下里  他还拥护两国方案
and privately, he's advocating for a two-state solution.
我们还能再指望他冒多大风险
How much further can we expect him to stick his neck out?
到这儿来
Hey, come here.
-你给他取名了吗  -熊熊
- Did you name him yet? - Bear.
-熊熊  -她在那里
- "Bear".  - There she is.
我听说你跟外公刚才和小熊一起玩呢
I heard that you and grandpa were hanging out with the bears.
我们还吃了冰激凌
Then we had ice cream,
但我不喜欢我的那个
But I didn't like mine,
外公就把他的给我了
So grandpa gave me his.
-真棒  -我来抱她
- That's nice. - Here, I got her.
-谢谢你能照顾她  杰克  -不客气
- Thanks for watching her, Jack.  - Of course.
我们之前谈的事  我想了很多
Listen, I've been thinking a lot about what we talked about.
我已经决定了
And I've made up my mind.
我想要和你一起搬回洛杉矶
I want to move back to Los Angeles with you.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really?  - Yeah.
我有个朋友  开了家私人安保公司
I got a friend who's got a private security firm.
他答应给我份咨询的工作
Said he'd give me some consulting work.
我还可以租他的房子
He's also got a place I can rent.
爸爸  我都不知说什么好了
Dad, I don't know what to say.
过来抱抱
Come here.
你什么都不用说
You don't have to say anything.
今晚接我去机场就行了
Just give me a ride to the airport tonight.
你想今晚和我们一起走吗
Wait, you're coming with us tonight?
如果方便的话
If it's okay.
斯蒂芬
Stephen.
他今晚和我们一起走
He's coming with us tonight.
我还有一点东西要打包
And I've just got a few more things to pack.
我本来东西就不多
I don't have very much.
一小时后  我就可以去酒店找你们
I can be at your hotel in about an hour.
太棒了  我们现在就回去打包
That's perfect. We can get back and finish packing ourselves.
外公和你一起飞回洛杉矶  好不好啊
It'll be all right if I fly back to Los Angeles with you?
-耶  -耶
- Yay! - Yay!
走吧  我送你们到车上
Come on. I'll walk you to the car.
走吧
Okay. Let's go.
-好哦  -我抱着她
- Yay! - I got her.
-好的  -我们要上车了
- Okay.  - We're going in the car.
我帮你系好安全带
Get your belt done up...
爸爸  我真高兴你能答应
Dad, I am so glad that you're doing this.
我也高兴
Me, too.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- I love you.  - Love you.
伙计们  一小时后见
Okay, guys, I'll see you in an hour.
-再见  -再见  小乖乖
- See you.  - Bye, sweetheart.
再见
Bye!
各位下午好
Good afternoon, everyone.
下午好
Good afternoon.
记者会召开之前  我有几件事宣布一下
All right, just a few things before we get started here.
泰勒总统和哈桑总统在秘书长的引荐后
Presidents Taylor and Hassan will each make a statement
将各自签署一项声明
after they've been introduced by the secretary-general.
随后是提问环节
The Q&A will follow,
希望各位严格围绕相关问题提问
but I want you to keep your questions strictly on topic.
显而易见  会议将在高度安保措施下进行
For obvious reasons, we're all operating under heightened security measures,
所以  除非你特想尝尝锁喉的感觉
so, unless you've been dying to know what a chokehold feels like,
请一定将证件放在身上醒目位置
keep your credentials visible at all times. All right?
就说这些了
That's all for now.
梅瑞狄斯·里德  记者
Meredith Reed, press.
您的证件无效
It's invalid.
什么
What?
不可能
It can't be invalid.
你能再检查一遍吗
Can you double check?
我已试过了  女士  你的证件被注销了
I did, ma'am. Your credentials have been revoked.
谁注销的
Revoked by whom?
这我无法得知
I don't have that information.
肯定是有地方弄错了
Okay, this has to be some sort of mistake.
你认得我  我天天都来参加此会议的
You do remember me. I've been here every day.
请退到一边  女士
Please step aside, ma'am.
国务卿卡宁刚才来找我
I just talked to Secretary of State Kanin.
他同意由国际原子能组织监察
He's agreed to IAEA inspectors.
好消息
That's good news.
有个附加条件
There is a condition attached.
他们坚持
They're insisting that
监察小组的领导要由美国人担任
the head of the verification team be an American.
我觉得这条可以接受  你认为呢
I think we can live with that, don't you?
你知道我的立场
You know where I stand.
为和平之名  我们已牺牲太多
We've already surrendered too much in the name of peace.
说"牺牲"太极端了  法哈德
Surrender is a strong word, Farhad.
我们牺牲了什么
And what have we surrendered really,
不过是对核武器的野心
apart from our nuclear ambition?
这还不够吗
Isn't that enough?
运作六千台离心机的确能带来政治筹码
Spinning 6,000 centrifuges is good for political maneuvering,
但也会拖垮我国的经济
but it's helping to bankrupt our country.
事实上
The truth is,
真正慷慨的不是我们
we are not the ones being so generous.
泰勒总统正准备取消经济制裁
President Taylor is lifting economic sanctions,
并愿意提供几十亿美元的援助项目
and offering an aid package worth billions of dollars.
我们的目的都已达到  法哈德
We got everything we wanted, Farhad.
但愿这不是骗局
As long as it's not a trick.
你好
Hello.
你好  很抱歉为这种小事烦扰你
Hi. I'm sorry to bother you with something so mundane,
我被拒之门外了
but I'm stuck outside.
被拒了
Stuck?
我的新闻采访资格证被注销了
My press credentials have been revoked.
我也不知道怎么回事
I don't know what happened.
我会解决的
I'll take care of it.
你确定
Are you sure?
当然
Of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
晚些时候  你还有空接受采访吗
Will you, uh, will you still have time for the interview later?
可以  新闻发布会后
Yes. After the press conference.
我非常期待  总统先生
I'm looking forward to it, Mr. President.
我也一样
So am I.
恢复里德小姐的安检通行证
Reinstate miss Reed's clearance.
我只是
I was only...
照做就是
Just do it.
奥马
Omar,
人们已经开始谈论你和这记者的事
people are starting to talk about you and this reporter.
他们说什么
And saying what?
里德小姐作为记者  为报社做我的专访
Miss Reed is a journalist and she's profiling me for her newspaper.
你对她有感情了
But you have feelings for her.
我对她很友好而已
I'm friendly with her.
随你怎么想
Think whatever you like.
这女人对我或对和平进程  没有任何威胁
This woman poses no threat to me or the peace process.
在这里或许没有
Not here maybe,
但在我们国家  你会因此声名狼藉
but back in our country you'll be torn apart.
毛拉会说  你被西方腐蚀了
The Mullahs will say that you have been corrupted by the west.
你怎么看  法哈德
What do you say, Farhad?
我有吗
Have I?
我有被西方所腐蚀吗
Have I been corrupted by the west?
你知道我不会相信的
You know I don't believe that.
但你要记住自己是已婚
But you are married.
达莉亚很久以前  就不是我妻子了
Dalia hasn't been a wife to me for a long time.
这不是行为不检的理由
That's no excuse to be reckless.
我没有任何行为不检
I've done nothing reckless.
我没做过
去恢复里德小姐的安检通行证吧
Just reinstate Miss Reed's clearance now.
我会的
I'll see to it.
维克多
Victor.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
你怎么找到我的
How the hell did you find me?
我一向消息灵通  杰克
I was always resourceful, Jack.
你也是你欣赏我的地方
That's what you liked about me.
赶紧进来
Get in here.
坐好
Take a seat.
发生了什么
What happened?
我需要你的帮助
I need help.
你需要的是救护车
You need an ambulance.
不  别打电话
No, no, don't call.
这样正中他们下怀
That's what he's waiting for.
-有人监听着急救频道  -谁
- He's listening to the emergency channels.  - Who?
听说我  杰克  我有重要情报
Just listen to me, Jack. I have information.
我唯一能帮你的  就是给你叫辆救护车
The best I can do for you, Victor, is get you an ambulance.
我早不干了  不再为政府工作了
I'm out. I don't work for the government anymore.
我这情报  你绝对想听
Oh, this you're going to want to hear.
为什么
Why?
为什么  因为你总能做出正确的选择
Why? Because you're the guy who always does the right thing.
有人策划了一项重大刺杀行动
There's a big hit going down.
刺杀谁
On who?
联合国大厦里的哈桑总统
President Hassan at the UN.
他即将遇刺
He's getting taken out.
-几时  -今天
- When?  - Today.
在他和泰勒总统签下条约之前
Before he can sign this thing with Taylor.
你瞧  我就说你会感兴趣
You see? I told you you'd be interested.
你怎么知道这些的
How do you know this?
是我负责把杀手偷渡入境的
I'm the one that got the hitter into the country.
我安顿好了他的一切
I've been setting him up with what he needs.
现在他打算干掉你
And then he tried to take you out.
杰克  反恐小组里只有你和我打过交道
Look, Jack, you're the only one at CTU I ever did business with.
我要你给他们打电话  为我担保
I need you to call them, vouch for me,
帮我和他们达成协议
so I can cut a deal.
帮帮忙  杰克
Come on, Jack.
给我坐好
Keep your seat.
我发誓  这事千真万确
Look, I swear, this is real.
有人试图阻止
Someone is trying to make sure
这份和平协议的签订
that this peace agreement does not happen.
先把枪给我  再说别的
I'm not doing anything until you give me your weapon.
你最好别给我耍花招
Better not be screwing with me.
我没有  我发誓
I'm not. I swear, I'm not.
杀手是谁  叫什么名字
Who's the hitter? What's his name?
杀手是谁
Who's the hitter?!
我不知道他的名字
I don't know his name.
-好像是俄罗斯人  -不够
- He's Russian or something.  - Not good enough.
-杀手是谁  -听我说
- Who is the hitter?! - Look.
我知道怎么在刺杀行动前找到并阻止他
I know how to find him and stop him before he makes the hit.
但达成协议之前  我不会透露半个字
But I'm not saying another word until I make my deal.
你该庆幸我退休了
You're lucky I'm retired.
我是科尔·奥迪斯
This is Cole Ortiz.
叫辛格小队移动到东北角
Move Singer's team to the northeast quadrant,
告诉他  从现在起
and tell him, from now on,
每15分钟给我汇报一次情况
I want updates every quarter hour.
确认后打给我
Get back to me with confirmations.
黑斯廷斯要你把联合国大厦的巡逻范围
Hastings wants you to expand the patrol perimeter around the UN
再增加400米
another quarter mile.
我很高兴他这么想
I'm glad that's what he wants,
但我的人手只勉强够覆盖目前的巡逻范围
but I barely have enough men to cover the perimeter now.
我想法找纽约警察来帮忙巡逻
I'll see if I can get NYPD to help you cover.
丹娜
Uh, Dana?
我姐姐说  她给你留言了好几次
My sister.. She said she left you a couple of messages.
商量伴娘礼服的事
Something about bridesmaids' dresses.
我告诉她  你的语音信箱可能出了点问题
I told her there was probably something wrong with your voicemail.
我收到留言了
I got her messages.
只是没时间回复  这加班加的
I just haven't had a chance. These double shifts...
我修改了联合国大厦的巡逻方案
I revised the patrol protocols at the UN.
下发任务前  先给你过目
Thought you might like to take a look at it before I distributed it.
好  我看看
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
我会给你姐姐回电话的  我保证
I will call your sister back, I promise.
该死  到底是什么问题
Damn it, what is the problem?
冲击维护
Percussive maintenance?
我的网络应用程序教授
That's what my network apps professor
看到我砸电脑时  给起的名
called it when I hit my computer.
能帮忙吗
Can I help?
我刚拿到最新修订的发布会出席名单
I just got the revised attendee list for the press conference.
来不及完成面部识别
I can't get the facial recognition done in time.
你单独一个个地扫描
Oh, you're running each person through individually.
其实可以批量识别
You can do them in a batch.
但是资料格式不匹配
Not if the data's in different formats.
老黄历了  现在改进了
Well, that used to be true, but here.
我说过  向他人求助并不丢脸
Like I said, there's no reason to be shy about asking for help. Okay?
别着急  你很快就能跟上  你行的
Don't worry. You'll catch up. You're doing great.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我是奥布赖恩
O'brian.
克罗伊  是我杰克
Chloe, it's jack.
金好吗  你告诉她洛杉矶的事了吗
How's Kim? Did you tell her about LA?
谈过  我现在没法细说
Yeah, but I can't go into that right now.
我要跟头儿讲话
I need to speak to the director.
黑斯廷斯先生正在通话中
Mr. Hastings is on the phone,
他很讨厌被别人打断
and he really doesn't like to be interrupted.
告诉他事关刺杀哈桑总统
Well, tell him it's regarding a plot to assassinate president Hassan.
看看能否引起他的关注
See if that gets his attention.
好的  稍等
Okay, hold on.
给我联合国大厦的层图  西侧视角
All right, now, give me an overlay on the UN, view from the west.
再给我安全控管小组的分布图
Now, overlay the distribution of security teams, please.
很好
That looks good.
给我事件报告与卫星图像的比对结果
Now, give me a comp with incident reports and Satellite imaging.
打搅一下  黑斯廷斯先生
Excuse me, Mr. Hastings.
盖瑞  稍等一下
Gary, hold on for a second.
杰克·鲍尔在三线  他说有事向您报告
Jack Bauer's on line three. He says he needs to talk to you.
鲍尔
Bauer?
事关暗杀哈桑总统
It's about a plot against president Hassan.
我想您会接听这个电话
I thought you'd want to take the call.
盖瑞  我等下再打给你
Gary, I'll call you back.
鲍尔先生  我是布赖恩·黑斯廷斯
Mr. Bauer, this is Brian Hastings.
黑斯廷斯先生  我以前的线人说
Mr. Hastings, I'm with an informant that I used to run who's claiming
他有关于刺杀哈桑总统行动的情报
he's got intel on an assassination attempt on president Hassan.
而且行动就在今天
He says it's going to take place today.
我们已接获多起关于威胁和平会谈的举报
We've received several threats in regard to the peace conference.
可以想象
I can only imagine.
我的线人名叫维克多·阿鲁兹
My informant's name is Victor Aruz.
他是我在撒拉扎尔行动中的线人
I used him in the Salazar op.
-你应该能找到他的档案  -查一下
- You should be able to pull his file.  - Pull it up.
他手臂中枪  说是暗杀者干的
He's been shot in the arm-- he claims by the assassin.
我认为这事决不能等闲视之
Look, I don't think this is something you should take lightly.
阿鲁兹先生想要怎样的回报
And what does Mr. Aruz want in return for his information?
反恐小组的保护以及豁免权
CTU protection and immunity.
他太贪了  鲍尔先生
That's a lot to ask, Mr. Bauer.
你调出他的档案了吗
Have you pulled his file yet?
没有
No.
黑斯廷先生  我了解这混蛋
Mr. Hastings, I know this son of a bitch,
直觉告诉我  你需要对此事引起警觉
and my instinct is telling me that you need to pay attention to this.
光凭你的直觉还不够  鲍尔先生
I need more than your instinct, Mr. Bauer.
这里不再是你熟知的反恐小组了
CTU isn't the organization you knew.
也罢  但你听好了
Okay, fine, but understand this:
倘若哈桑总统有什么不测
if anything happens to president Hassan,
我有责任向泰勒总统报告
I will be obligated to call president Taylor
告诉她  我曾向你提供此情报
and tell her that I tried to provide you with this intel,
但却被你无视了
and you ignored it.
调个档案怎么要这么久
What is taking so long for the file?
抱歉  我还在搜索卷宗
Sorry. I'm still searching through the archives.
黑斯廷斯先生  你现在就得答复我
Mr. Hastings, I need your answer now.
你打算询问阿鲁兹吗
Are you bringing Aruz in or not?
让我跟他说话
Let me talk to him.
我打开免提
I'll put you on speaker.
说吧
Go ahead.
阿鲁兹先生
Mr. Aruz,
我需要更多细节以证实你的情报
I'm gonna need some other details to corroborate your story.
暗杀者干掉了我的两个手下
The hitter took out two of my guys.
曼纽尔·艾斯克巴  毛利西奥·特列斯
Manuel Escobar and Mauricio Tellez.
找警局查查
Check with the cops.
我们会的
We will.
鲍尔先生  你们在哪
Mr. Bauer, where are you?
西18大道  1145号
1145 West 18th.
我会派直升机去接你们
I'll send a chopper to pick you up.
最近的停机坪在12区
The closest helipad to you is... the 12th precinct.
五个街区外
That's five blocks away.
鲍尔先生  你能把他带到那里吗
Can you get him there, Mr. Bauer?
好
Yeah.
我的人20分钟内抵达
I'll have a team there in 20 minutes.
切记不要使用官方频道
Make sure you don't use official channels.
我们认为杀手已监控了紧急通讯频段
We believe the assassin is monitoring emergency bandwidth.
了解
Got it.
召集通讯小组和战术小组
Gather comm and tactical,
告诉他们有紧急任务
tell them we've got a situation.
走
Let's go.
找到你了
There you are.
身材还不错
Now that doesn't suck.
-阿洛  -什么事
- Arlo.  - Yeah.
快点  黑斯廷斯召集紧急简报
Come on. Hastings called an emergency briefing.
若被他抓到你干这个
And if he ever catches you doing that,
你会被开除的
you're gonna be out of a job.
那也值了
Be worth it.
我想这就是爱
I think this might be love.
赶快
Now.
这里是反恐小组
This is CTU
把无人机A31与A32的控制权
transferring control of Drones A31 and 32
转移给HS空中指挥部
to HS aerial command.
收到
Yeah, roger that.
转移确认
Offload confirmed.
发生紧急情况
All right, we've got a situation.
科尔  我要你弄架直升机去接个人
Cole, I need you to scramble a chopper for a pickup.
可我还没分配完最新巡逻任务
Yeah. I haven't finished distributing the new patrol parameters.
此任务优先
This is a priority.
我要接的人是谁
Who am I picking up?
线人  自称握有关乎哈桑总统性命的情报
Someone who claims to have intel about a threat to president Hassan.
情报准确吗
How good is the intel?
根据杰克·鲍尔所说  很准确
Well, according to Jack Bauer, very.
杰克·鲍尔
Jack Bauer?
他正护送线人前来
He's delivering the informant.
杰克·鲍尔是谁
Who is Jack Bauer?
地点在市中心  克罗伊会给你坐标方位
Location's downtown; Chloe's sending you the coordinates.
带支小队一起去
Take a small team with you.
托雷斯的人可供支配
Torres' people are free.
是  长官  我还需一队人来掩护降落
Yes, sir. And I'll need a second team to secure the landing.
一队人足够了
One team will be enough.
我们用无人机来保护地面行动
We'll use a drone to protect the ground operation.
阿洛  安排一架无人机跟着直升机
Arlo, scramble a drone alongside the chopper.
全方位保护降落地点
Full spectrum coverage of the landing zone
包括空中范围
as well as the air corridor.
明白
Done.
安全  快走
We're clear. Come on.
调度  我是2354组
Dispatch, this is unit 2354.
请讲  2354
Go ahead, 2354.
发现与被盗车辆牌照一致的车辆
Got a plate match on a stolen vehicle.
车牌号为S-N-E-1-5-C-5
Plate Sierra, November, Echo, one, five, Charlie, five.
车身和挡风玻璃上有弹孔
Got bullet holes in the windshield and body.
就是他
That's him.
收到  你的位置在哪
Roger that. What's your location?
车停在18大道  9大道西侧
Vehicle's parked on 18th, just west of Ninth Avenue.
我们会处理好
We'll take care of it.
你可以吗
Will you?
或者还是我亲自来动手
Or am I going to have to step in?
你最好现在就告诉我
Now would be the time to tell me.
阿鲁兹死定了
Aruz is a dead man, sir.
-我向你保证  -很好
- You have my word.  - Good.
谢谢
Thank you.
打扰了  总统阁下
Excuse me, madam president.
哈桑总统接受了我们关于监察的反提案
President Hassan accepted our counterproposals on inspections.
真是好消息啊
That is great news.
下一场会议结束时
By the end of this next session,
应该就能签订协议了
we may have a signed agreement.
此举成就不凡  艾莉森
It's an extraordinary accomplishment, Allison.
有什么问题吗
Is something wrong?
我在想亨利
I was thinking about Henry.
与伊斯兰共和国达成和平共识
Achieving a comprehensive peace agreement with the Islamic Republic
是我和他多年前的共同梦想
was something that he and I talked about years ago.
真希望他能在此共襄盛举
I wish that he were here to share the moment.
你很惊讶吗
You surprised?
鉴于他要求离婚时的行为
Considering his behavior during the divorce,
是的  我很惊讶
Yes, I am surprised.
他做得太过分了
He went out of his way to hurt you,
尤其是在媒体面前
especially in the press.
他很生气  伊桑
He was angry, Ethan.
我把我们的女儿送进了监狱
I sent our daughter to prison.
你只是拒绝掩盖一起谋杀
You refused to cover up a murder.
奥利维亚理应为其行为负责
Olivia was responsible for what happened--
与他人无关
No one else.
但是  倘若我和他互换位置
Still, if the the situation had been reversed,
我可能也会和亨利一样
I might've felt the same way as Henry.
抱歉打扰了
Sorry if I'm interrupting,
反恐小组的布赖恩·黑斯廷斯来电
but I just talked to Brian Hastings at CTU.
出什么事了  罗伯
What's going on, Rob?
根据线人提供的情报显示
They have someone who claims he's got information
有人要刺杀哈桑总统
about an assassination plot on Hassan.
情报准确吗
How real is the threat?
准确到需要通知您
Real enough to loop you in.
情报是由杰克·鲍尔提供的
This informant came to them through Jack Bauer.
我以为杰克早就不干了
I thought that Jack was out of all of this.
他怎么卷进来了
How did he get involved?
据目前所知  是线人主动找到的他
As far as I can tell, this informant came to him.
如果您愿意签署豁免协议
We'll know more once the informant signs an immunity deal,
我们就能知道更多
provided you authorize it.
新闻发布会的场地安全系数如何
How secure is the venue for the press conference?
非常高  我刚提高了警戒级别
Very. And I just raised the alert level.
但我们要在会议开始之前
But we need to set up a call to inform Hassan about the threat,
及时电话告知哈桑
ideally before the conference gets started.
我们不能告诉哈桑
We can't tell Hassan.
至少要瞒到新闻发布会结束后
Certainly not before the press conference.
为什么
Why not?
他可能会出于自身安全考虑  弃协议而逃
Well, he might scuttle everything, out of concern for his own safety.
哈桑不是小孩子
Hassan's a big boy.
他经过大风大浪才有今天的地位
He's used to taking risks or he wouldn't be here;
这点你清楚
You know that.
况且  若哈桑发现我们瞒着他
Plus, if Hassan finds out we knew about this and didn't tell him,
我们这一年来建立起的信任将毁于一旦
then all the trust we've built up over the last year goes out the window,
他必然会退出谈判
And then he'll pull out of talks.
坦白说  到时我不会怪他
And frankly, I wouldn't blame him.
我会好好考虑的
I'll think about it.
谢谢你们两位
Thank you both.
总统阁下  我要告诉你
Madam president, I'm telling you,
隐瞒哈桑的结果不堪设想
holding this back from Hassan could be disastrous.
我说了  我会考虑的  罗伯
I said I'd think about it, Rob.
谢谢
Thank you.
伊桑
Ethan...
抱歉  我刚才对你太冲了
Listen-- sorry if I went after you a little hard in there.
我只是阐明观点而已
I was just making my point.
不必道歉  罗伯
No need to apologize, Rob.
我之所以向总统举荐你
I recommended you to the president
就是因为你直言敢谏
because you're not afraid to speak up.
她需要这样的人
She needs that.
但我有时仍会过于激动  我...
Yeah, well, still, I know I can get carried away; I...
没关系  孩子  我还活得好好的
Don't worry, kid... I ain't dead yet.
我了解自己的身体
I can handle myself.
和你对抗  也绰绰有余
Even up against you.
宝贝  是我
Hey, sweetheart, it's me.
我们快收拾好了  你在路上了吗
Hey, we're almost finished packing. Are you on your way?
出了点状况  我要晚一点到了
Something came up. I'm gonna be a little late.
多晚
How late?
我们还是机场见吧
I think I should meet you at the airport.
没出什么事吧
Is everything okay?
没事
Yeah.
确定吗
Are you sure?
金  我保证一切都好
Kim, I promise everything's fine.
你要跟我们回来  泰瑞非常开心
Well, Teri is so excited that you're coming back with us.
你出发后  给我打个电话
Just, uh, let me know when you're on your way.
好的  谢谢  宝贝
Okay, thanks, sweetheart.
提高警惕
Keep your eyes open.
还差两个街区就到了
The precinct's two blocks away.
我们从这抄近道
Let's cut through here. Come on.
联邦航空局已清理出专用航线
The FAA's cleared a route
并已告知所有相关机构  我们即将起飞
and informed all relevant agencies that we will be in the air.
了解
Copy that.
好运
Good luck.
阿鲁兹的档案  在专用数据库里
Aruz's file-- it was in a proprietary database.
所以才会花这么久
That's why it took so long.
那也不该难倒你  你已经来了一个月了
Still, that shouldn't have thrown you-- you've been here a month.
不到一个月
Almost a month,
我需要重新熟悉每个主系统的接口
and I've had to relearn the interface on every major system here;
一切都不同了
everything's changed.
你适应不顺利  我了解
And you're having trouble adapting, I understand.
我不怀疑你的智商
But I don't think it's a question of your intelligence.
谢谢
Thanks.
我认为你是在闹情绪
I think it's ambivalence.
闹情绪
Ambivalence?!
你来工作的唯一原因
I know the only reason you took this job
是你的丈夫被裁员了
was because your husband was downsized.
-我说错了吗  -不
- Am I wrong?  - No!
我是说  是的
I mean, yes.
求你了  再给我点时间跟上速度
Please, just give me a little more time to get up to speed here.
黑斯廷先生  我需要这份工作
Mr. Hastings, I need this job.
可以
Fair enough.
但我追求的是效率
But I'm all about efficiency,
若你的表现还是差强人意
so if your performance doesn't improve,
你最好三思  是否要待下去
You may want to rethink working here.
我想我说的已经够清楚了
Now, I trust this has been clarifying.
当然
Sure.
你真要效率的话
If you really wanted to be more efficient,
我若不尽快赶上进度  你就炒了我
If I don't catch up soon, I'm going to be fired?
你的航线是西南方向直航  越过河流
Your flight path is a straight shot southwest over the river,
12区已确认
and the 12th precinct has confirmed
停机坪安全可用
that their helipad is clear and operational.
全航线由通讯网和卫星双重覆盖
Comm net and satellite coverage of your flight, both legs,
还有无人机全程空中保护
and full-time aerial from the Drone
你干嘛这样看着我
why are you looking at me like that?
哪样
Like what?
我只是想确保万无一失
Look, I just want to make sure nothing's wrong.
如果所说  万无一失啊
Nothing's wrong, like I said.
小心点
Just be careful, okay?
会的
I will be.
准备好了吗
You ready?
嗯
Yeah.
我们出发吧
Let's go
你们该敲定个日子了
You know, maybe she should finally set a date.
她有点畏缩了
She's getting cold feet.
给我闭上你的嘴
How about you shut up
专心做好自己的工作
and just focus on your assignment?
撑住  维克多
Come on, Victor!
维克多  维克多
Victor? Victor!
撑住
Stay with me.
维克多  撑住
Victor, stay with me!
撑住
Stay with...
妈的
Damn it.
撑住
Stay with me!
我们要重新压住伤口
We're going to need to recompress the wound.
如若谈成  这份协定将会给
If successful, the agreement could be the beginning
长期动荡的中东地区带来真正长久的和平
of a real lasting peace in a long-troubled region.
泰勒总统和哈桑总统按计划
Presidents Taylor and Hassan are scheduled
将于几分钟后  召开联合新闻发布会
to give their first joint press conference in just a few minutes,
我们将为您现场直播
and we'll carry that live.
稍后  克里斯蒂安·杜美尼将为您专题报道
In a moment, Christiane Doumany will have a report
列举此前为中东和平所做的种种失败尝试
on the history of the many failed attempts at a mideast peace,
以及此次和谈的特殊之处
And why this accord may be different.
该走了
It's time to go.
告诉你父亲  我会赶到的
Tell your father I'll be right there.
我等你一起
I'll wait until you're done.
他不相信我会准时到
He doesn't trust me to be on time.
他当然相信你
Of course he trusts you.
你何时起也变得这么会说谎了
When did you become such a good liar?
不必为你父亲说话  达莉亚
You don't have to defend your father, Dalia.
他能照顾好自己
He can take care of himself.
你看上去真漂亮  达莉亚
You look beautiful, Dalia.
你看上去也很英俊
And you look handsome.
我们演戏也得注意个度
Let's not pretend any more than we have to.
很抱歉  让你看到这一幕
I'm sorry you had to see that.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
我亲爱的凯拉
My dear Kayla.
我们该走了
We should go.
是的
Yes.
让她通过
Let her through.
谢谢
Thank you.
我把对他说的话  同样对你说一遍
I will tell you the same thing that I told him.
你若不想他的奋斗成果付之东流
Unless you want to destroy everything that he's worked for,
就离他远点
stay away from him.
打扰了  夫人
Excuse me, ma'am.
哈桑总统快来了
President Hassan is on his way.
你不打算告诉他  他已成为刺杀目标
You're not going to tell him he's being targeted.
总统阁下  我很抱歉
Madam president, I'm sorry.
你这么做会在一天内将我们长期...
You risk destroying in a single day all the--
罗伯  我明白你想说什么
Rob,You've made your point.
你已经说了多次
More than once.
相信我  我也不愿意
And believe me, I don't like keeping this
向哈桑总统隐瞒这个消息
from president Hassan any more than you do.
那就告诉他啊
Then tell him.
总统先生
Mr. President.
女士们
Ladies.
我的参谋长你们见过了吧
You've met my chief of staff?
当然了
Of course.
你好  总统先生
Hello, Mr. President.
我一直没机会感谢您
I haven't had the chance to thank you
在监察问题上所做的妥协
for compromising on the verification issue.
这是为保大局之举
It was the right thing to do.
您若不介意
If you don't mind,
我想向两位介绍新闻发布会的安排
I'd like to brief you both on the format of the press conference.
秘书长将会在简单陈述后
The secretary-general will be introducing you both
向大家介绍两位
after some brief remarks.
发布会本身不会超过25分钟
The conference itself shouldn't take any longer than 25 minutes or so.
手压住伤口
Put your hand on it.
我们走
Let's go.
就快到了
We're almost there.
别动
Don't move!
有人报告说你们发生了争端
Got a call that you two are having a problem down here.
怎么回事
What's up?
警官  我叫杰克·鲍尔
Officer, my name is Jack Bauer.
我正为反恐小组运送此人
I'm transporting this man on behalf of CTU.
这个线人对国家安全至关重要
He's an informant vital to national security.
-向局里汇报  -听我说
- Call it in.  - Listen to me.
企图杀他的人已监视了所有的紧急频道
The men that are trying to kill him are monitoring all emergency channels.
不要让他对讲汇报
Do not let him make that call.
闭上嘴  靠着垃圾桶站好
Shut up and get against the dumpster. Now!
至少请带我们进辖区  届时可以证实
At least take us into the precinct. We can verify everything there.
趴下  快
Get down, now!
该死
Damn it!
我掩护你  跑进门里去
I'm going to cover you. Make a run for the door.
准备好  跑  跑
You ready? Go! Go!
别停下  我没子弹了
Keep moving, I'm out of bullets.
克罗伊  我是杰克  直升机还要多久
Chloe, it's Jack. How far out is the helicopter?
两分钟  杰克  怎么了
Two minutes. Jack, what's wrong?
我们遭到攻击
We're under attack.
给我接通直升机小队的指挥官
I need you to put me in touch with whoever's in command of that unit.
好的  是奥迪斯探员
Okay. It's agent Ortiz.
他是外勤组的指挥
He's the head of field ops.
-出什么事了吗  -是的
- Is there a problem?  - Yes.
黑斯廷先生  接应方面出了问题
Mr. Hastings, we have a situation with the pickup.
一直往屋顶上跑  快
Keep going to the roof. Now.
无论如何都别停下  只管跑
Don't stop for anything. Keep going.
奥迪斯探员  杰克要和你通话
Agent Ortiz, you're on with Jack Bauer.
收到
Roger.
怎么了  鲍尔先生
What's going on, Mr. Bauer?
两名持枪杀手在追我们
We're being pursued by two shooters.
我们根本到不了辖区
There's no way we're going to make the precinct.
我们在西21大道的一幢楼里
We're in a building on West 21st,
靠近第九大道  第三栋楼
three doors in from Ninth Avenue.
我们立即飞往你的位置  保持通话
We're heading to your position now-- stay on the line.
我们正在另寻接应点
We're looking for an alternate pickup.
收到
Copy that.
在那儿  那栋停车场的屋顶可以降落
Right there-- the roof of that parking structure might work.
你能放大一点吗
Can you zoom in closer?
卫星正在刷新图像  稍等
The satellite's refreshing. It'll take a minute.
我立刻派无人机前往
I'm moving the drone there now.
你们那栋楼边上有一栋停车场
There's a parking structure next to the building you're in.
那里的屋顶应该可以降落
Roof looks clear to land.
你听到了吗  科尔
Did you get that, Cole?
我看到了
Yeah, I see it.
鲍尔先生  从你那栋楼的八楼
Mr. Bauer, looks like you can access that roof
可以到达那个屋顶
from the eighth floor of the building you're in.
-你还有多久  -90秒
- How far out are you?  - 90 seconds.
收到
Copy that.
别来晚了
Don't be late.
维克多  维克多  听我说
Victor... Victor, listen to me.
你得把杀手的所有信息都告诉我
You got to tell me everything you know about the hitter,
万一我们逃不走  我也好上报
so I can call it in in case we don't make it.
如果我活不了  我才不管发生什么事
If I don't make it, I don't care what happens.
送我去反恐小组
Get me to CTU.
你他妈的总是这么混蛋  快走
You always were a son of a bitch. Come on.
快走
Come on. Let's go.
待在那儿
Stay there.
封锁通往屋顶的全部入口
Lock down access points to the roof!
-敌人呢  -死了
- Where are the hostiles?  - They're dead.
赶快带他走  他失血很多
You need to get him out of here. He's losing a lot of blood.
我是科尔·奥迪斯  很荣幸见到你
Cole Ortiz. It's an honor to meet you.
感谢你所做的一切
Thanks for doing this.
黑斯廷要你回反恐小组询问
Look, Hastings wants to debrief you back at CTU.
我不回反恐小组
I'm not going back to CTU.
把他送到  我任务已完成
I delivered him, I'm done.
-不行  鲍尔先生  -我还要赶飞机
- No, Mr. Bauer...  - I got a flight to catch.
这就走了
That's it?
趴下
Get down!
奥迪斯  报告情况
Ortiz, report in.
奥迪斯探员
Agent Ortiz?
奥迪斯探员  你那边情况怎样
Agent Ortiz, what's your status?
奥迪斯探员
Agent Ortiz?
杰克  回话
Jack, come in.
杰克  你能听到我吗
Jack, can you hear me?
有人吗  回话
Anyone, come in.
维克多
Victor.
维克多  维克多  醒醒
Victor, Victor, come on.
撑住  撑住
Stay with me, stay with me.
听我说
Listen to me.
你不想就这样死的
you don't want to die like this.
做正确的选择
Do the right thing.
把你知道的都告诉我
Tell me what you know.
杀手有内应
The hitter has someone on the inside.
那人和哈桑关系密切
Close to Hassan.
告诉我名字
Give me a name.
名字  告诉我名字
Give me a name. Give me a name!
维克多
Victor...
维克多  内应是谁
Victor, who's on the inside?
维克多
Victor!
醒醒
Come on.
醒醒  醒醒
Come on, come on.
不要
No.
他死了
He's dead.
不行
No.
她弟弟注销了我的通行证
The brother revoked my clearance,
我让哈桑又重新恢复了
But I had Hassan reinstate it.
不  我知道
No, I know.
我知道进度落后了
I know I'm behind schedule.
我会完成的
But it'll get done.